oddstuffmagazine.com 2019-04-08

# Privacy

Odd Stuff Magazine respects your privacy. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name & e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Odd Stuff Magazine.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates. Odd Stuff Magazine will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you Do Not enter it on any of the forms on Odd Stuff Magazine.

Odd Stuff Magazine is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies :**  A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Odd Stuff Magazine to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Odd Stuff Magazine does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds. Google and DoubleClick DART Cookies – Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site,  Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet, Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Visitor Tracking**  : Odd Stuff Magazine makes use of analytical softwares such as Google Analytics for statistical purposes. For the purpose of stats, your browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured, we use Google Analytics with anonymized IP (Internet Protocol) Address, we do not capture your IP. We at Odd Stuff Magazine use this information only for statistical purpose and do not share it with any third party.

**User Comments**  : Odd Stuff Magazine does not allow users to comment on the site.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Odd Stuff Magazine and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.

In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Odd Stuff Magazine have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.  Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

For any other information please [contact us](https://oddstuffmagazine.com/contact-us).

**Odd Stuff Magazine collects some Personal Data from its Users.**

 **Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:**

**Analytics**  
Google Analytics with anonymized IP  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

**Contacting**  
MailChimp Mailing list / Newsletter  
Personal Data: email address

**Traffic optimization and distribution**  
CloudFlare  
Personal Data: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

Contact Owner and Data Controller  
privacy@oddstuffmagazine.com

Odd Stuff Magazine respects your privacy. Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name & e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Odd Stuff Magazine.

We have a strict no spam policy and do not send you any emails, unless you subscribe to receive email updates. Odd Stuff Magazine will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you Do Not enter it on any of the forms on Odd Stuff Magazine.

Odd Stuff Magazine is not responsible for the content of external Internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies :**  A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Odd Stuff Magazine to recognize you each time you visit this site(customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Odd Stuff Magazine does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as news feeds. Google and DoubleClick DART Cookies – Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site,  Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet, Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Visitor Tracking**  : Odd Stuff Magazine makes use of analytical softwares such as Google Analytics for statistical purposes. For the purpose of stats, your browser, screen resolution, operating system are captured, we use Google Analytics with anonymized IP (Internet Protocol) Address, we do not capture your IP. We at Odd Stuff Magazine use this information only for statistical purpose and do not share it with any third party.

**User Comments**  : Odd Stuff Magazine does not allow users to comment on the site.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Odd Stuff Magazine and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information.

In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Odd Stuff Magazine have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.  Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

For any other information please [contact us](https://oddstuffmagazine.com/contact-us).

**Odd Stuff Magazine collects some Personal Data from its Users.**

 **Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:**

**Analytics**  
Google Analytics with anonymized IP  
Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

**Contacting**  
MailChimp Mailing list / Newsletter  
Personal Data: email address

**Traffic optimization and distribution**  
CloudFlare  
Personal Data: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

Contact Owner and Data Controller  
privacy@oddstuffmagazine.com

### Like Odd Stuff on Facebook

[yuzo_related]
